(走过的路)
爸爸走了
Look, dad's gone now.
我们得继承他的遗志
We have to carry out his legacy.
那就是
And that means hunting down
能猎杀多少凶鬼恶灵杀多少
as many evil sons of bitches as we possibly can.
萨姆  小心
Sam. Look out.
不
No.
萨姆
Sam.
我猜猜  你要拿自己的灵魂换吗
Let me guess, you're offering up your own soul?
你只需要复活萨姆
All you gotta do is bring Sam back.
我给你一年  就一年
I'll give you one year and one year only.
如果你企图想办法钻空子
If you try and welch or weasel your way out,
那交易取消
then the deal is off.
你有多确定
How certain are you
你复活的
that what you brought back...
是百分百纯粹的萨姆
is 100 percent pure Sam?
发生了什么
What the hell just happened?
那是魔鬼之门  地狱的大门
That's a Devil's Gate, a damn door to hell.
希望你们准备好了
Hope to hell you boys are ready.
因为战争刚打响了
Because the war's just begun.
(如今)
(伊利诺伊州  橡树园)
[邪恶力量 第3季第1集]
(一周后)
(浮士德博士)
(十字路口魔鬼)
(非常七人组)
- 喂  - 萨姆
- Hello? - Sam.
- 鲍比  - 你干什么呢
- Bobby. - What are you doing?
就那样呗
You know, same old, same old.
你又埋头看那本书了
You buried in that book again?
萨姆  你想打破迪恩的恶魔交易
Sam, you wanna break Dean free of that demon deal...
答案是不会写在哪本书里的
you ain't gonna find the answer in no book.
那要去哪找  鲍比
Then where, Bobby?
小子  我知道就好了
Kid, I wish I knew.
你哥哥呢
So where's your brother?
- 做民调呢  - 什么
- Polling the electorate. - What?
没事
Never mind.
你们准备上路吧
Well, you boys better pack it up.
我可能终于有所发现了
I think I finally found something.
迪恩
Dean?
迪恩  你醒着吗
Dean, you conscious?
鲍比打来了  他觉得我们可能...
Bobby called and he thinks that maybe we...
天啊
Oh, God.
把你的刀给我
Let me see your knife.
干什么
What for?
我要把眼睛挖出来
So I can gouge my eyes out.
那是种美妙自然的行为  萨姆
It's a beautiful, natural act, Sam.
我才不想看到你那个样子  迪恩
It's a part of you I never wanted to see, Dean.
多谢你让我跟绿箭双胞胎
I appreciate you giving me a little quality time
共度美妙时光
with the Doublemint Twins.
不客气
Yeah, no problem.
是吗
Really?
我得说  我还以为
I gotta say, I was expecting a
你会疲倦地叹气  或翻白眼呢
weary sigh or an eye roll. Something.
不  不会
No, not at all.
你有权享乐一下
You deserve to have a little fun.
这我非常同意
Well, I'm in violent agreement with you there.
- 鲍比查到了什么  - 不多
- What's Bobby got? - Not much.
内布拉斯加州林肯近郊有作物枯萎和蝉群
Crop failure and a cicada swarm outside of Lincoln, Nebraska.
可能是恶魔预兆
Now, it could be demonic omens...
也可能只是作物和虫害问题
Or it could just be a bad crop and a bug problem.
对  但这是我们唯一的线索
Yeah. But it's our only lead.
有怪异死亡吗
Any freaky deaths?
鲍比是没查到
Nothing Bobby could find.
- 至少暂时还没有  - 好奇怪啊
- Not yet, anyway. - It's weird, man.
魔鬼之门打开那晚
I mean, the night the Devil's Gate opened,
有多少座城市上空
all these weird old storm clouds
出现了奇怪的暴雨云
were sighted over how many cities?
- 17座  - 17座
- Seventeen. - Seventeen.
按说早该是《现代启示录》了
You'd think it'd be Apocalypse Now.
可这都五天了  还什么都没有
It's been five days and bupkes.
恶魔在等什么啊
What are the demons waiting for?
我也不知道
Beats me.
简直要把我逼疯了
It's driving me crazy.
告诉你  如果战争要来了
I tell you, if it's gonna be war,
真希望它赶紧开始
I wish it'd just start already.
我不知道
I don't know, man.
许错愿要后悔的
Careful what you wish for.
(内布拉斯加州  林肯近郊)
听到那蝉鸣了吗
Hear those cicadas?
那绝不是好兆头
Well, that can't be a good sign.
是啊  的确
No. No, it can't.
早餐就吃上培根奶酪汉堡了吗
So we're eating bacon cheeseburgers for breakfast, are we?
嗯
Well,
卖了灵魂
sold my soul.
只剩一年活头了
Got a year to live.
我是不担心胆固醇什么的了
I ain't sweating the cholesterol.
鲍比  你怎么想
So, Bobby, what do you think?
这里是发生圣经里那样的瘟疫了吗
We got a biblical plague here or what?
去看看吧
Well, let's find out.
这里似乎是蝉群聚集的地方
Looks like the swarm's ground zero.
糖果电报
Candygram!
太恶心了
That's awful.
- 这绝对不是好兆头  - 是啊
- That so can't be a good sign. - No.
你听到了吗
You hear that?
这本该是我的生日派对
It's supposed to be my birthday party.
天啊
Oh, my God.
奶奶在列宾客名单
Grandma is making out the invitation list.
苏·艾伦要雇...
Sue Ellen is gonna hire...
- 鲍比  这是怎么回事  - 我不知道
- Bobby, what the hell happened here? - I don't know.
- JR要用...  - 看看有没有硫磺
- And J.R. is gonna use this... - Check for sulphur.
很盛大
Big deals.
你要买我的衣服
And now you're gonna buy my clothes.
我恨这个家庭
I hate this family!
艾萨克  塔玛拉
Isaac? Tamara?
鲍比  你怎么在这里
Bobby, what the hell are you doing here?
- 我也想问你们呢  - 你好吗  鲍比
- I could ask the same. - How are you, Bobby?
喂
Hello?
我都流血了
Bleeding here.
珍妮  是吗  名字好美
So, Jenny, is it? That is a beautiful name.
我妹妹也叫这个
That's my sister's name.
嗯
Yeah.
亲爱的
Honey.
她的声音跟你也像
She sounds like you.
圣檀木呢
Where's the Palo Santo?
你放哪了
Well, where'd you leave it?
我不知道  亲爱的  所以才问你
I don't know, dear, that's why I'm asking.
圣檀木
Palo Santo?
就是圣木
It's holy wood.
来自秘鲁
From Peru.
对恶魔有毒  就像圣水
It's toxic to demons, like holy water.
能钉住那些混蛋  让你有时间驱魔
Keeps the bastards nailed down while you're exorcising them.
谢谢  亲爱的
Thank you, dear.
要是没有我  你连脑袋都能丢
You'd lose your head if it wasn't for me.
你们结婚多久了
So how long you two been married?
到6月有八年了
Eight years this past June.
一起猎魔的家庭...
The family that slays together...
是啊  这我有体会
Right, I'm with you there.
你们怎么入行的
So how'd you get started?
你们不...
You're not...
抱歉  我不该...
I'm sorry. It's not...
- 我不该问  - 不不
- It's none of my business. - No, no, it's...
没事的
It's all right.
珍妮  如果你人有声音那么美
Well, Jenny, if you, uh, look as pretty as you sound...
那我很想跟你一起喝苹果马丁尼
then I'd love to have an appletini.
嗯  再联系你
Yeah. Call you.
- 那是死因裁判官的技术员  - 怎么样
- That was the coroner's tech. - And?
听好
Get this.
那一家人  死因
That whole family, cause of death:
脱水和饥饿
Dehydration and starvation.
没有捆绑迹象  没有暴力和挣扎的痕迹
There's no signs of restraint. No violence. No struggle.
他们就坐下  然后再没起来
They just sat down and never got up.
但几步之外的厨房里就有充足的食物呢
But there was a fully-stocked kitchen just yards away.
是啊  怎么回事  恶魔袭击吗
Right. What is this, a demon attack?
如果是  我是没见过这种情况
If it is, it's not like anything I ever saw
我可见过不少呢
and I've seen plenty.
那现在怎么办  我们该怎么做
Well, what now? What should we do?
- 我们不做什么  - 什么意思
- We're not gonna do anything. - What do you mean?
你们看上去不错
You guys seem nice enough...
但这可不是《史酷比狗》
but this ain't Scooby-Doo
我们不怎么跟其他人合作
and we don't play well with others.
我觉得我们如果合作
Well, I think we'd cover a lot more ground
能更高效些
if we all worked together.
无意冒犯
No offense.
但我们可不要跟打开了
But we're not teaming with the damned fools...
魔鬼之门的蠢货合作
who let the Devil's Gate get opened in the first place.
- 还无意冒犯呢  - 艾萨克
- No offense? - Isaac.
你难道没犯过错吗
Like you've never made a mistake.
嗯嗯
Yeah. Yeah.
把钥匙锁在车里过
Locked my keys in the car.
把白衣服洗成粉的过
Turned my laundry pink.
但没带来过世界末日
Never brought on the end of the world, though.
好吧  我受够了
All right. That's enough.
各位  这样没什么好处  迪恩
Guys, this isn't helping. Dean.
听着  现在外面还有几百个恶魔呢
Look, there are a couple hundred more demons out there now.
我们不知道他们在哪
We don't know where they are.
什么时候会出击
When they'll strike.
全世界的猎人加起来
There ain't enough hunters in the world
都不足以应付这种局面
to handle something like this.
你们给我们带来了战争
You brought war down on us.
- 我们所有人  - 好了
- On all of us. - Okay.
你的大男子主义真是够了
That's quite enough testosterone for now.
我去看看
I'll check that.
我们有34号的
We've got it in a 34.
好的
Yeah. Okay.
- 行吗  - 应该行
- Is that all right? - I think so.
不好意思
Excuse me?
怎么了
Yes?
那鞋真漂亮
Those are nice shoes.
是啊
Yeah.
是很漂亮
They are nice.
那鞋真漂亮
Those are nice shoes.
是吧
Aren't they?
- 我想要  - 抱歉  最后一双了
- I want them. - Sorry, last pair.
打扰一下
Excuse me?
我想要那双鞋
I want those shoes.
你疯了吗  不行
What, are you crazy? No.
什么  干什么...
What? What the...?
大概10分钟前
About 10 minutes ago.
- 最好叫格里瑟姆来  - 查查看
- I think you better call Grissom. - Check that.
外面发生的事
You know, what happened outside
让人意识到生命多么脆弱
makes you realize how fragile life really is.
所以不能浪费人生的一分一秒
You gotta make every second count.
失陪一下  好吗
Excuse me a minute, would you?
- 嗯  - 好
- Sure. - Yeah.
迪恩  你干什么呢
Dean, what are you doing?
安慰伤心的人
Comforting the bereaved.
- 你在干什么  - 工作
- What are you doing? - Working.
死尸  可能是恶魔袭击  什么的
Dead body. Possible demon attack, that kind of stuff.
萨姆  抱歉  我...
Sam, I'm sorry. It's just, you know,
我时日无多了
I don't have much time left, and, uh...
我不能浪费一分一秒
I gotta make every second count.
嗯  好吧
Yeah, right. All right.
- 抱歉  - 接受你的道歉了
- I'm sorry. - Apology accepted.
收拾得这么干净  鲍比  你是探员吗
Looking spiffy, Bobby. What were you, a G-man?
刚从地检官办公室来
Returning from the DA's office.
- 跟嫌疑人谈过了  - 是吗
- Just spoke to the suspect. - Yeah?
你怎么看
So what do you think there?
她是被附身了吗
Was she possessed or what?
看来没有
Don't think so.
并没有任何一般的迹象
There's none of the usual signs. No
没断片  没失控
blackouts, no loss of control.
完全清醒  她就是特想要那双鞋
Totally lucid. Just think she really wanted those shoes.
还洒了她一身圣水  以防万一
Spilled a glass of holy water on her, just to be sure.
没反应
Nothing.
或许她就是个普通的疯子
Well, maybe she's just some random whack job.
如果这是独立事件还有可能
If it had been an isolated incident, maybe. But
但先是那一家  现在又这一出
first the family, now this?
我相信很多事
I believe in a lot of things.
但不包括巧合
Coincidence ain't one of them.
你们在这里有发现吗
Did you boys find anything around here?
没有硫磺
No sulphur.
- 什么都没有  - 或许有点什么
- Nothing. - Well, maybe something.
看
See?
我也在工作
I'm working.
有什么发现吗
Anything interesting?
还不能确定
I don't know, yet.
可能就是个普通人
Might just be a guy.
也可能是我们要找的人
Or it might be our guy.
几点了
What time is it?
午夜12:07
Seven past midnight.
- 你确定我们找对地方了吗  - 不确定
- You sure this is the right place? - No.
但我一整天都拿这家伙的丑脸
But I spent all day canvassing this stupid town...
在这破地方到处打听
with this guy's stupid mug and...
据说他在这家破酒吧喝酒
supposedly he drinks at this stupid bar...
- 这不好笑  - 嗯
- It's not funny. - Yeah.
好吧
All right, so...
无名氏叫沃特·罗森
So John Doe's name is, uh, Walter Rosen.
来自芝加哥以西的橡树园
He's from Oak Park just west of Chicago.
大概一周前失踪
Went missing about a week ago.
- 魔鬼之门打开那晚吗  - 对
- The night the Devil's Gate opened? - Yep.
你觉得他被附身了
So you think he's possessed?
很有可能
Well, it's a good bet.
怎么  他走到一个人面前  摸下那人
So, what, he just walks up to someone, touches them...
那人就变成疯子了吗
and they go stark raving psycho or something?
那些冲出了大门的恶魔
Those demons that got out of that Gate,
他们肯定有各种我们没见识过的本事
they're gonna be able to do all kinds of things we haven't seen.
我们放出来的那些恶魔吗
You mean, the demons we let out.
两位
Guys.
好了  上场吧
All right. Showtime.
等等
Wait a minute.
怎么了
What?
我刚说什么了
What did I just say?
我们不知道这人有什么本事
We don't know what to expect out of this guy.
我们该跟踪他  探探虚实
We should tail him till we know for sure.
怎么  他杀了人
So he kills someone
而我们只闲坐在这里吗
and we just sit here with our junk in our hands?
我们死了更没用
We're no good dead.
我们不清楚情况  就不能轻举妄动
We're not gonna make a move untill we know what the score is.
鲍比  那办法恐怕不行了
Bobby, I don't think that's an option.
为什么
Why not?
该死
Damn it.
- 多谢  - 不客气
- Thanks a lot. - You're welcome.
把车开到后面
Pull the car in back.
我们很快就能完事
We'll be right out.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道
I know.
你想干什么
What do you think you're doing?
我就是去解手
I'm just hitting the head.
不
No.
我是问
I mean,
你为什么跑来这里
what do you think you're doing here?
我不喜欢我的酒吧里有猎人
I don't like hunters in my bar.
伙计  你真是来错了地方
Man, you really walked into the wrong place.
等等
Hold on.
我喜欢那女的
I like the girl.
我也想要个那样的女人
Wish I had me a girl like that.
我能想到上千件我想对她做的事呢
I could think of about a thousand things I'd like to do to her.
你的脏手别想碰她
You're not gonna lay one filthy finger on her.
我有东西给你
I have something for you.
(水管清洁剂)
来
Here.
喝点吧  我请
Have a drink on me.
艾萨克
Isaac?
请你的
On the house.
艾萨克
Isaac.
Isaac!
艾萨克  不要  亲爱的
Isaac, no! Baby, please!
他倒下了
He's down.
好了  亲爱的  该你了
All right, honey. Your turn.
不
No.
- 艾萨克  不要  - 来  我们得走了
- Isaac! No! - Come on, we gotta go!
- 不  他死了  - 艾萨克  不要
- No, no, no, he's dead, he's dead. - Isaac, no, baby!
- 上车  - 宝贝
- Get in the car. - Baby.
- 艾萨克  - 走吧
- Isaac! Isaac! - Let's go!
迪恩  快走
Dean, come on!
走走走
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
我说  我们要回去
And I say we're going back.
等一下的
Listen, just hold on a second.
我留下我丈夫在地上流血
I left my husband bloody on the floor.
好吧  我明白  但我们不能回去
Okay, I understand that, but we can't go back.
好啊
Fine,
那你们留下
then you stay.
但我要回酒吧去
But I'm heading back to that bar.
我陪她去
I'll go with her.
- 这是自杀  迪恩  - 那又如何
- It's suicide, Dean. - So what?
我反正也死了
I'm dead already.
你要怎么杀他们
How are you gonna kill them?
枪不好使
You can't shoot them.
刀不好使
You can't stab them.
他们也不会一个个等着被驱魔
They're not just gonna wait in line to get exorcised.
- 我不在乎  - 我们都不知道他们有多少个
- I don't care! - We don't even know how many of them there are.
我们知道
Yeah, we do.
他们有七个
There're seven.
你们知道我们面对的是什么情况吗
Do you have any idea who we're up against?
不知道  什么情况
No. Who?
七宗罪
The seven deadly sins.
他们鲜活的本尊
Live and in the flesh.
"盒子里是什么"
"What's in the box?"
布拉德·皮特的《七宗罪》  没看过吗
Brad Pitt? Se7en? No?
- 这是什么  - 《宾斯费尔德恶魔分类》
- What's this? - Binsfeld Classification of Demons.
1589年  宾斯费尔德确认了七宗罪
In 1589, Binsfeld ID'd the seven sins.
不仅仅是人性缺点  还是真正的恶魔
Not just as human vices, but as actual devils.
那家人  他们被懒惰碰了
The family. They were touched by Sloth.
那个购物者
And the shopper.
那是嫉妒干的
That's Envy's doing.
我们旁边房间里那位
The customer we got in the next room.
我起初无法判断  直到艾萨克的事
I couldn't suss it out at first, until Isaac.
他被贪食碰了
He was touched with an awful gluttony.
我才不在乎
I don't give a rat's ass
他们是三个臭皮匠还是四顶尖合唱团
if they're the Three Stooges or the Four Tops.
我要把他们都杀掉
I'm gonna slaughter every last one of them.
我们已经按你的方式试过了
We already did it your way.
你们准备不充分就冲了进去  结果呢
You burst in there half-cocked and look what happened.
这些恶魔都有五百年没上来过了
These demons haven't been top side in half a millennium.
是中世纪  黑暗时代的恶魔
We're talking medieval, Dark Ages.
我们根本没应付过类似的东西
We've never faced anything close to this.
所以我们要缓一缓
So we are gonna take a breath...
想好接下来该怎么办
and figure out what our next move is!
我为你的丧亲表示遗憾
I am sorry for your loss.
你们知道我是谁了
So you know who I am, huh?
是的  我们没觉得有啥了不起
We do. We're not impressed.
你们为什么来这里
Now, why are you here?
你们想要什么
What are you after?
他问你问题了
He asked you a question.
你们想要什么
What do you want?
我们已经得到我们想要的了
We already have what we want.
什么
What's that?
我们出来了
We're out.
我们自由了
We're free.
因为你们  到处都是我们的人
Thanks to you, my kind are everywhere.
"我名叫群  因为我们数目众多"(马可福音)
"I am legion, for we are many."
所以我只是在庆祝
So me, I'm just celebrating.
开开心
Having a little fun.
- 开心  - 对
- Fun? - Yeah.
开心
Fun.
有些人喜欢钩针编织  有些人喜欢打高尔夫
See, some people crochet, others golf.
我呢
Me...
我喜欢看人的里子
I like to see people's insides...
翻到外面来
on their outside.
- 我要像杀狗一样杀了你  - 拜托
- I'm gonna put you down like a dog. - Please.
你们真觉得你们比我强吗
You really think you're better than me?
你们谁是无罪之人  能丢第一块石头
Which one of you can cast the first stone, huh?
你吗  迪恩
What about you, Dean?
你几乎是...
You're practically a...
行走的贪食和淫欲的广告牌
A walking billboard of gluttony and lust.
还有塔玛拉
And Tamara.
那么多愤怒
All that wrath?
这正是你和艾萨克
It's the reason you and Isaac
成为猎人的原因吧
became hunters in the first place, isn't it?
因为沉溺于愤怒之中
It's so much easier to drink in the rage...
要比面对多年前的真相轻松得多
than to face what really happened all those years ago.
我说中了吧  你们还说我们是罪恶
My point exactly. And you call us sins.
我们才不是罪恶
We're not sins, man.
我们是自然的人类直觉
We are natural human instinct.
随你们怎么压抑  否认我们
And you can repress and deny us all you want...
但事实就是  你们只是动物
but the truth is, you are just animals.
淫荡  贪婪
Horny, greedy...
饥饿
hungry,
暴力的动物
violent animals.
知道吗
And you know what?
你们也会如动物般被屠杀
You'll be slaughtered like animals too.
其他人
The others?
他们会来找我的
They're coming for me.
或许吧
Maybe...
但他们别想找到你了
but they're not gonna find you...
因为你要下地狱了
because you'll be in hell.
谁送这小丑上路
Someone send this clown packing.
我很荣幸
My pleasure.
我们恐怕不需要担心怎么猎他们了
I don't think we're gonna have to worry about hunting them.
什么意思
What does that mean?
我觉得那小丑可能说对了
I think maybe this joker's right.
他们会来猎我们的
They're gonna be hunting us,
他们不会轻易放弃的
and they're not gonna quit easy.
你们带上塔玛拉跑吧
You guys, why don't you take Tamara and head for the hills.
我留下  拖住他们  争取时间
I'll stay back, slow them down, buy a little time.
你疯了  迪恩
You're insane, Dean.
不可能的  好吗
Just forget about it, okay?
萨姆是对的
Sam's right.
他们有六个呢
There's six of them, guys.
我们寡不敌众  武力不足
We're outmanned, we're outgunned.
天明前就会被团灭
We'll be dead by dawn.
或许吧  但我们跑去哪都会被他们找到
Maybe, but there's no place to run that they won't find us.
听着  如果我们要死
Look, if we're going down,
我们也要死在一起  好吗
we're going down together, all right?
那我们别让他们太轻松了
Well, let's not make it easy for them.
恶魔被逐出那人了
Demon's out of the guy.
那人呢
And the guy?
没活下来
He didn't make it.
开始了
Here we go.
塔玛拉
Tamara!
救我
Help me!
救救我
Please!
塔玛拉
Tamara!
我跑出来了
I got away,
但我伤得很重
but I'm hurt bad.
我需要救助
I need help.
那不是他
It's not him.
是有个恶魔附身了他的尸体
One of those demons is possessing his corpse.
亲爱的
Baby!
你为什么不放我进去
Why won't you let me in?
你刚刚丢下了我
You left me behind back there.
你怎么能那么做
How could you do that?
我们发过誓
We swore
在密歇根州的那座湖边  记得吗
at that lake in Michigan, remember?
我们发誓绝不抛下彼此
We swore we would never leave each other.
- 他怎么会知道  - 别冲动  塔玛拉
- How did he know that? - Steady, Tamara.
别冲动  塔玛拉
Steady, Tamara, steady.
你要把我丢在外面吗
You're just gonna leave me out here?
你要任我死去吗
You're just gonna let me die?
你就是这种人吧  亲爱的
I guess that's what you'd do, dear.
就像那晚  那些玩意冲进了我们家
Like that night those things came to our house.
抓住了我们的女儿
Came for our daughter.
你也任她死去了
You just let her die too.
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch!
塔玛拉  不
Tamara, no!
你不是艾萨克
You're not Isaac.
人这辈子可不该又胖又醉又傻  小子
Fat, drunk and stupid is no way to go through life, son.
你是淫欲吧
I suppose you're Lust.
亲爱的  你希望我是什么我就是什么
Baby, I'm whatever you want me to be.
- 好吧  别过来  - 否则呢
- Yeah, all right. Just stay back. - Or what?
有道理
Good point.
我不会伤害你
I'm not gonna hurt you.
现在还不会
Not yet.
除非你希望我伤你
Not unless you want me to.
约翰尼来了（出自《闪灵》）
Here's Johnny.
拜托
Come on.
你真觉得那样的东西
You really think something like that
能骗过我这样的人吗
is gonna fool someone like me?
我啊
I mean, me?
我猜猜
Let me guess.
你是骄傲
You're Pride.
万罪之源
The root of all sin.
你...
And you...
是萨姆·温彻斯特
are Sam Winchester.
没错  我听说过你
That's right, I've heard of you.
我们都听说过你
We've all heard of you.
天才
The prodigy.
小子国王
The Boy King.
看你这幅样子  我得说
Looking at you now, I gotta tell you,
别信那些吹捧
don't believe the hype.
你觉得我会向你这样的可怜虫人类俯首称臣吗
You think I'm gonna bow to a cut-rate, piss-poor human like you?
我可是有骄傲的
I have my pride, after all.
你的黄眼朋友也死了
Now with your yellow-eyed friend dead,
看来我什么都不用做了  是吧
I guess I don't really have to do a damn thing, now, do I?
你现在是众矢之的  人人可杀了
You're fair game now, boy, and it's open season.
你
You.
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
我是刚救了你的姑娘
I'm the girl that just saved your ass.
我也救了你
Well, I just saved yours too.
回见了  萨姆
See you around, Sam.
等等
Wait!
你觉得她会没事吗
Think she's gonna be all right?
不  绝对不会
No, definitely not.
你气色好差
Well, you look like hell warmed over.
你试试驱魔一整夜  看你什么感觉
Well, you try exorcising all night, see how you feel.
有活下来的吗  鲍比
Any survivors, Bobby?
那个漂亮姑娘和胖小子能活下来
Well, the pretty girl and the heavy guy. They'll make it.
要做一辈子心理咨询了  但总算能活
Lifetime of therapy bills ahead, but still.
这些可怜虫就惨了
It's more than you can say for these poor bastards.
鲍比  那把刀
Bobby, that knife.
什么样的刀能杀恶魔
What kind of blade can kill a demon?
昨天的话  我会说没有这种东西
Yesterday, I'd have said there was no such thing.
我要再问一遍
I'm just gonna ask again.
那无名小妞是谁
Who was that masked chick?
其实  更令人不安的问题是
Actually, the more troubling question would be...
一个姑娘怎么打架比你厉害
how come a girl can fight better than you?
三个恶魔呢  迪恩
Three demons, Dean.
一起上
At once.
你晚上能睡得着就行  伙计
Whatever it takes to get you through the night, pal.
如果你想要个让人不安的问题  我有一个
Well, if you want a troubling question, I got one for you.
什么问题
What's that?
如果我们放出了七宗罪
If we let out the seven deadly sins,
那我们还放出了什么
what else did we let out?
是啊  这问题是让人不安
You're right, that is troubling.
回头见了
See you gents around.
塔玛拉
Tamara?
世界现在可怕多了
World just got a lot scarier.
你多保重
Be careful.
你们也是
You too.
你们多留意预兆
Keep your eyes peeled for omens.
- 我也会的  - 没问题
- I'll do the same. - You got it.
鲍比
Bobby?
我们能赢得这场战争吧
We can win this war, right?
下次再见了
Catch you on the next one.
我们去哪
So where to?
我不知道  或许去路易斯安那州吧
I don't know. I was thinking Louisiana, maybe.
- 现在还不到狂欢节吧  - 嗯
- Little early for Mardi Gras, isn't it? - Yeah.
听着  我刚刚跟塔玛拉聊天
Listen, I was talking to Tamara...
她提到什里夫波特城外有个女巫术师
and she mentioned this Hoodoo priestess just outside Shreveport...
她或许能帮我们解决你的...
that might be able to help us out, you know, with your...
恶魔交易
Your demon deal.
不了
Nah.
Nah?
什么意思"不了"
What does that mean, "Nah?"
萨姆  巫术是无法打破这个交易的
Sam, no Hoodoo spell's gonna break this deal.
这是白跑
It's a goose chase.
- 我们不能确定  - 我们确定
- Yeah, but we don't know that. - Yes, we do.
算了吧  她帮不上忙
Forget it, she can't help.
- 这值得...  - 我们不去  就这么定了
- Look it's worth... - We're not going and that's that.
里诺怎么样
What about Reno?
知道吗
You know what?
我受够了
I've had it.
你一直很努力地对你好
I've been bending over backwards trying to be nice to you and...
我不在乎了
I don't care anymore.
- 没坚持多久呢  - 知道吗
- That didn't last long. - Yeah. Well, you know what?
我一直在努力保住你的命  迪恩
I've been busting my ass trying to keep you alive, Dean.
你却一副毫不在乎的样子
And you act like you couldn't care less.
怎么  你是想死吗
What? You got some kind of death wish or something?
- 不是那样的  - 那是什么样  迪恩
- No, it's not like that. - Then what's it like, Dean?
- 萨姆  - 拜托  告诉我吧
- Sam... - Please, tell me.
如果我们困住一个十字路口恶魔
We trapped a Crossroads demon.
欺骗它  想办法钻交易的空子
Trick it, try to welch our way out of the deal in any way,
你就会死
you die.
好吗
Okay?
你会死
You die.
那就是交易条件  没法绕过的
Those are the terms. There's no way out of it.
你敢想办法  上帝保佑
If you try to find a way, so help me God,
我会阻止你的
I'm gonna stop you.
你怎么能做这个交易  迪恩
How could you make that deal, Dean?
因为我受不了你死
Because I couldn't live with you dead.
- 做不到  - 那现在是我活  你死吗
- Couldn't do it. - So, what now? I live and you die?
就是这意思
That's the general idea, yeah.
那你是个伪君子  迪恩
Yeah, well, you're a hypocrite, Dean.
爸爸为你出卖灵魂时你是什么感受
How did you feel when Dad sold his soul for you?
因为我可记得你当时的样子
Cause I was there. I remember.
你痛苦不堪
You were twisted and broken
现在你又做了同样的事
and now you go and do the same thing.
对我做
To me.
你的做法很自私
What you did was selfish.
你是对的  是很自私
Yeah, you're right, it was selfish,
但我不介意
but I'm okay with that.
- 我介意  - 没办法
- I'm not. - Tough.
考虑到我为这个家做的一切  我觉得我有这权利
After everything I've done for this family, I think I'm entitled.
说实话  我累了  萨姆
Truth is, I'm tired, Sam.
我不知道  感觉就像隧道尽头有了光亮
I don't know. It's like there's a light at the end of the tunnel.
那是地狱烈火  迪恩
That's hellfire, Dean.
随便了
Well, whatever.
你活着
You're alive,
我好久以来第一次感觉良好
I feel good for the first time in a long time.
我还有一年活头了  萨姆
I got a year to live, Sam.
我想好好利用
I'd like to make the most of it.
怎么样  我们一起去杀些凶鬼恶灵
So, what do you say we kill some evil sons of bitches.
惹点麻烦吧
And we raise a little hell?
你真让人难以置信
You're unbelievable.
太对了
Very true.